Melville S. Munro Papers MS036
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Melville S. Munro Papers
1930 -- 1945
1858 -- 1959
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Munro, Melville S.
MS036
84.62 Linear Feet 118 boxes
808 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into fifteen series: Photographic history of Tufts College; Afield with a camera; Campus related activities; Photo inventories; Small photo albums; The scrap book; Tufts and the war; Tufts College History; War years at Tufts; The weather; Loose prints; Photographic History of Dramatics at Tufts College; Lantern slides; Boston Globe Currier and Ives Prints; and Tufts College history and technology.
Scope and Contents
This collection primarily consists of photographs of Tufts College and students taken by Melville Munro between 1930 and 1945. Munro arranged most images into albums by theme or topic. There are also some albums of clippings and publications on topics of interest to Munro in his teaching, including weather formations and electricity. Many of Munro's photographs have been cataloged separately at the item level.
Biographical / Historical
Melville S. Munro (1881-1945), a faculty member for more than three decades, made his most notable contributions to Tufts through his camera's lens. Munro was born in Charlestown, Massachusetts, on July 7, 1881. He graduated from Tufts College with a B.S. in electrical engineering in 1904. Following graduation, Munro was appointed as an assistant to the electrical engineering department. He became an instructor in the department in 1905 and was made a professor in 1913. During his thirty-seven years on the faculty, Munro worked as the college's official photographer, recording an almost complete pictorial history of campus and student life up until 1941.
Munro retired in 1941 and died at his summer home in Maine on June 1, 1945. His wife, Ruth Harmon, W1903, predeceased him in 1941. Both of their children, Lawrence, E1930, and Ella, J1935, attended Tufts.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Students; World War, 1914-1918; Alumni and alumnae; Faculty; University history; Munro, Melville S.
- Photographic history of Tufts College, 1904 -- 1946; MS036.001; 20.8 Linear Feet; 329 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains seventy-five photo albums created between 1913 and 1945 documenting daily, weekly, and annual activities around the Tufts College campus. Also includes sections Munro titled, "Horribles," campus events, celebrations, sports teams, and various student groups. Also includes the three volumes entitled: "Photographic history of Tufts College, landscape views."
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 1, 1913-09 -- 1915-01; MS036.001.001.00001 (Volume 1)
    Alpha Tau Omega frat house, pg 8.
    scrapbooks
    - William Richardson Sr. football pose, 1913; MS036.001.001.00001.00001; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Melville S. Munro Collection - MS036/001-001-pg. 9.
      Football; photographic print; Richardson, William Sr.
    - Football team, 1913; MS036.001.001.00001.00002; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Melville S. Munro Collection - MS036/001-001-pg. 5 (Richardson is holding the ball).
    - Football team: game against unidentified aggie college, 1914; MS036.001.001.00001.00003; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Melville S. Munro Collection - MS036/001-001-pg. 71.
      Football; photographic print
    - A college sing led by Leo Lewis, 1915; MS036.001.001.00001.01432; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Melville S. Munro Collection - MS036/001-001-pg. 141
      Student activities; Events; photographic print; Lewis, Leo R.; Bumpus, Hermon Carey
    - Professor Edward Rockwell, Professor Richard C. Smith and structural engineering students, 1915; MS036.001.001.00001.01433; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Edward Rockwell, Richard C. Smith; Melville S. Munro Collection - MS036/001-001-pg. 78
      Faculty; Students; photographic print; Rockwell, Edward; Smith, Richard C.; College of Engineering
    - Evening Party Association, 1913; MS036.001.001.00001.01434; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Melville S. Munro Collection - MS036/001-001-pg. 12
      Student activities; photographic print; Evening Party Association
    - Track squad, 1913; MS036.001.001.00001.01575; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      (left to right) Lawrence Howes Teel, James Henry Holden, Everett Austin Geer, Roland Grover Stafford or Henry Alexander Stafford, Robert Leston McLellan; Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 1, Box No. 1, Pg. 10
      People; Students; Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Teel, Laurence Howes; Holden, James Henry; Geer, Everett Austin; Stafford, Roland Grover; Stafford, Henry Alexander; McLellan, Robert Leston; Track
    - People crowded around "The Bubbler", 1914; MS036.001.001.00001.03460; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 1, Box No. 1, Pg. 54
      People; The Bubbler; photographic print
    - An evening band concert during Class Day activities, 1914; MS036.001.001.00001.03461; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Views; Class Day; photographic print; Department of Music
    - An evening band concert during Class Day activities, 1914; MS036.001.001.00001.03462; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
    - Richardson House girls, 1915; MS036.001.001.00001.03477; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 1, Box No. 1, Pg. 82
      People; Students; Houses; photographic print; Jackson College
    - Richardson House girls, 1915; MS036.001.001.00001.03478; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 1, Box No. 1, Pg. 82.
    - Jackson College varsity basketball team, outside Goddard Chapel, 1919; MS036.001.001.00001.04060; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 3)
      Print is in Munro collection, box 003, page 52.
      Students; Athletics; Women; People; photographic print; Jackson College; Basketball
    - Football team in front of Barnum Hall, 1913; MS036.001.001.00001.04208; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Image is in Munro Collection, Box 001, p. 5
      Students; Football; Athletics; photographic print; Black students
    - Junior class in front of Goddard Chapel, 1914; MS036.001.001.00001.04209; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 001, p. 30
      Students; photographic print; Black students
    - Football team, 1914; MS036.001.001.00001.04210; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 001, p. 63
    - Parade to class exercises, 1915; MS036.001.001.00001.04211; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 001, p. 91
      Students; Commencement; Events; photographic print; Black students
    - Football team in front of Barnum Hall, 1913; MS036.001.001.00001.04443; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 001, p. 4, #OA1a
      People; Men; Students; Football; Athletics; photographic print
    - Baseball player warming up before a game, 1914; MS036.001.001.00001.04444; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 001, p. 27, #B-1
      People; Men; Students; Baseball; Athletics; photographic print
    - Baseball player warming up before a game, 1914; MS036.001.001.00001.04445; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 001, p. 27, #B-4
    - Junior Day Sports, 1914; MS036.001.001.00001.04446; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 001, p. 35, #x57
      People; Students; Athletics; Track (Men's); Junior Day; photographic print
    - Football game, 1914; MS036.001.001.00001.04447; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 001, p. 71, #299
      People; Students; Athletics; Football; photographic print
    - Tufts v. Bowdoin football game, 1914; MS036.001.001.00001.04448; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 1)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 001, p. 72, #307
      People; Athletics; Football; Students; photographic print
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 2, 1915-12 -- 1918-05; MS036.001.002.00001 (Volume 2)
    Alpha Xi Delta. Alpha Omicron Pi photos of members, p37. Photos of Alpha Tau Omega members; Alpha Tau Omega frat house, pg 111.
    - Tyler, 14 June, 1916; MS036.001.002.00001.02950; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 2)
      Photographic History of Tufts College, vol. II (box 2), p. 34
      Athletics; Students; photographic print; Munro, Melville S.; Tufts College
    - Football team, October 26, 1915; MS036.001.002.00001.04212; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 2)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 002, p. 2
    - Football team, 1915; MS036.001.002.00001.04213; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 2)
    - Football team in front of Goddard Chapel, 1915; MS036.001.002.00001.04214; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 2)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 002, p. 1
    - Football team, November 19, 1916; MS036.001.002.00001.04215; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 2)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 002, p. 59
    - Football team, October 16, 1916; MS036.001.002.00001.04216; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 2)
    - Football player, McGee (fullback), October 19, 1917; MS036.001.002.00001.04217; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 2)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 002, p. 105
      Students; Football; Athletics; photographic print; Black students; McGee
    - Football team, October 17, 1917; MS036.001.002.00001.04218; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 2)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 002, p. 106
    - Football team, October 17, 1917; MS036.001.002.00001.04219; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 2)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 002, p. 107
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 3, 1918-05 -- 1920-05; MS036.001.003.00001 (Volume 3)
    Alpha Xi Delta photo of members, 138; Alpha Omicron Pi photo of members, p83. Photos of Alpha Tau Omega; Alpha Xi Delta, 12
    - Delta Upsilon on musical clubs, 1919-03-12; MS036.001.003.00001.02951; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 3)
      Munro Scrapbook: Photographic History of Tufts College, Vol. 3, Box No. 3, Pg. 46
      People; Students; Student activities; photographic print; Delta Epsilon
    - Student on graduation day, 1919-06-19; MS036.001.003.00001.04220; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 3)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 003, p. 96
      Students; Commencement; photographic print; Black students
    - Football team, 1919-10-28; MS036.001.003.00001.04221; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 3)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 003, p. 126
    - Football team, 1919-10-28; MS036.001.003.00001.04222; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 3)
    - Football team, 1919-11-21; MS036.001.003.00001.04223; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 3)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 003, p. 127
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 4, 1920-05 -- 1921-03; MS036.001.004.00001 (Volume 4)
    Alpha Omicron Pi photo of members, 55-56. Alpha Tau Omega, photos of members; Alpha Xi Delta, photos of members, 152
    - A "Horrible" in a barrel from the Junior class, 1918; MS036.001.004.00001.02952; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 4)
      The date is approximate. Photographic History of Tufts College, vol. IV (box 4), p. 49.
      Student activities; photographic print; Munro, Melville S.; Tufts College
    - The room of Miss Margolis, Start House, 1921; MS036.001.004.00001.02953; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 4)
      The date is approximate. Photographic History of Tufts College, vol. IV (box 4), p. 25.
      Students; photographic print; Jackson College
    - Jackson freshmen buttons, 1921; MS036.001.004.00001.02954; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 4)
      Munro Scrapbook: Photographic History of Tufts College, Vol. IV, Box No. 4, pg. 106.
      Students; Traditions; photographic print; Jackson College
    - Football team, 1919-11-21; MS036.001.004.00001.04224; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 3)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 003, p. 127.
    - Jackson College, class of 1920 in front of Goddard Chapel, 1920-05-01; MS036.001.004.00001.04225; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 4)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 004, p. 27
      Students; Women; Commencement; photographic print; Black students; Jackson College
    - Jackson College, class of 1920 in front of Goddard Chapel, 1920-05-01; MS036.001.004.00001.04226; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 4)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 004, p. 28
    - Premedical students, office record, 1920-10-29; MS036.001.004.00001.04227; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 4)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 004, p. 82
      Students; Men; Premedical education; photographic print; Black students
    - Premedical students, office record, 1920-10-29; MS036.001.004.00001.04228; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 4)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 004, p. 83
    - Premedical students, office record, 1920-10-29; MS036.001.004.00001.04229; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 4)
    - Football players, 1920-10-08; MS036.001.004.00001.04230; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 4)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 004, p. 85
    - Football players, 1920-10-08; MS036.001.004.00001.04231; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 4)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 004, p. 86
    - Football players, 1920-10-08; MS036.001.004.00001.04232; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 4)
    - Football player, Galloway, 1920-10-08; MS036.001.004.00001.04233; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 4)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 004, p. 89
      Students; Football; Athletics; photographic print; Black students; Galloway
    - Football player, Martin, 1920-10-08; MS036.001.004.00001.04234; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 4)
      Students; Football; Athletics; photographic print; Black students; Martin
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 5, 1920-03 -- 1921-06; MS036.001.005.00001 (Volume 5)
    Alpha Omicron Pi photo of members, p54-56; Alpha Xi Delta photos of members, 27
    - Tufts boxing, 1921-03-29; MS036.001.005.00001.01695; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 5)
      (contained in Photographic History of Tufts College, Vol. 5, pg. 32, box 005)
      Athletics; Boxing; photographic print
    - Woman's dorm room in Metcalf Hall, 1921; MS036.001.005.00001.01696; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 5)
      (contained in Photographic History of Tufts College, Vol. 5, pg. 110, box 005)
      Dormitories; photographic print
    - Band playing in Goddard Chapel, 1921-05-14; MS036.001.005.00001.01697; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 5)
      (contained in Photographic History of Tufts College, Vol. 5, pg. 118, box 005)
      photographic print
    - Senior vs. Junior Field Hockey Game during Jackson Day, 1921-06-04; MS036.001.005.00001.01698; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 5)
      (contained in Photographic History of Tufts College, Vol. 5, pg. 139, #2844, box 005)
      Athletics; Field Hockey; photographic print; Jackson College
    - Students boxing, 1921-03-29; MS036.001.005.00001.04235; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 5)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 005, p. 32
      Students; Boxing; Athletics; photographic print; Black students
    - Students boxing, 1921-03-29; MS036.001.005.00001.04236; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 5)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 005, p. 33
    - Students boxing, 1921-03-29; MS036.001.005.00001.04237; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 5)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 005, p. 34
    - End of 220 yard dash, 1921-05-28; MS036.001.005.00001.04238; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 5)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 005, p. 128
      Students; Track (Men's); Athletics; photographic print; Black students
    - End of 440 yard dash, 1921; MS036.001.005.00001.04239; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 5)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 005, p. 129
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 6, 1921-06 -- 1922-04; MS036.001.006.00001 (Volume 6)
    Alpha Tau Omega photos of members, 112, 9; Alumni day pp.28-30
    - Three Jackson tennis players, 1922; MS036.001.006.00001.02818; Unknown (Volume 6)
      From the Melville S. Munro scrapbooks, Vol. VI, pg. 132
      Athletics; Tennis (Women's); People; photographic print
    - Class of 1925 in front of Eaton Hall, March 14, 1922; MS036.001.006.00001.04240; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 6)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 006, p. 121
      Students; Men; photographic print; Black students
    - Class of 1924 in front of Eaton Hall, March 13, 1922; MS036.001.006.00001.04241; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 6)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 006, p. 123
    - Class of 1924 in front of Eaton Hall, March 13, 1922; MS036.001.006.00001.04242; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 6)
    - Class of 1925 track team in front of Eaton Hall, March 24, 1922; MS036.001.006.00001.04243; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 6)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 006, p. 146
      Students; Track (Men's); photographic print; Black students
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 7, 1922-04 -- 1923-04; MS036.001.007.00001 (Volume 7)
    Alpha Omicron Pi photos of members, 8-9; Alumni day photos, pp 80-81
    - East Hall inmates, June 6, 1922; MS036.001.007.00001.04255; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 7)
      Print is in Munro Collection, box 007, p. 66, #3475
      Students; Men; Buildings; photographic print; Black students
    - East Hall inmates, June 6, 1922; MS036.001.007.00001.04256; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 7)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 007, p. 67, #3476
    - Engineers, 1926; MS036.001.007.00001.04257; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 7)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 007, p. 85, #3627
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 8, 1923-05 -- 1924-03; MS036.001.008.00001 (Volume 8)
    Alpha Omicron Pi photo of members, p22-24. Alpha Tau Omega photos of members, pg. 116-117; Alumni day photos, pp 38-40
    - Tufts men's basketball team, March 4, 1924; MS036.001.008.00001.02720; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 63)
      Photograpic History of Tufts, Vol. 8: Box 008, pg. 138
      People; Athletics; Basketball; photographic print; Men's basketball team
    - Women students in front of Eaton Hall, November, 1923; MS036.001.008.00001.04258; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 8)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 008, p. 114, #4097
      Students; Women; photographic print; Black students
    - Relay team, January 17, 1924; MS036.001.008.00001.04259; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 8)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 008, p. 128, #4171
      Students; Men; Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Black students
    - Relay team, January 17, 1924; MS036.001.008.00001.04260; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 8)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 008, p. 128, #4170
    - Relay team, January 17, 1924; MS036.001.008.00001.04261; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 8)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 008, p. 129, #4173
    - Relay team, January 17, 1924; MS036.001.008.00001.04262; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 8)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 008, p. 129, #4172
      Students; Men; Track (Men's); photographic print; Black students
    - Class of 1927 men's basketball team, March 4, 1924; MS036.001.008.00001.04263; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 8)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 008, p. 137, #4195
      Men; Students; Athletics; Basketball; photographic print; Black students
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 9, 1924-03 -- 1924-10; MS036.001.009.00001 (Volume 9)
    Alumni day De Molay Band photo, p.80; Alpha Xi Delta, photos of members, p68-69; House party photos of Alpha Tau Omega, pg 25; Alpha Omicron Pi photos of members, p48-51. Alpha Tau Omega photos of members 141-142
    - Jackson field hockey, October 8, 1924; MS036.001.009.00001.02719; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 9)
      Photograpic History of Tufts, Vol. 9, Box 9, Pg. 125
      People; Students; Athletics; Field Hockey; photographic print; Jackson College
    - Claude Randolph Taylor, October 7, 1924; MS036.001.009.00001.02949; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 9)
      Photographic History of Tufts College, volume 9, pg. 103.
      Athletics; Football; Students; photographic print; Black students; Taylor, Claude Randolph
    - The library staff, including Blanche H. Hooper, Ethel M. Hayes, and two unidentified women, September 11, 1924; MS036.001.009.00001.03465; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 9)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 9, Box No. 9, Pg. 96
      People; Staff; Libraries; photographic print; Hooper, Blanche; Hayes, Ethel M.; Library
    - Organ grinder, September 11, 1924; MS036.001.009.00001.03466; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 9)
      People; slide (photograph)
    - Jackson field hockey team, October 8, 1924; MS036.001.009.00001.03471; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 9)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 9, Box No. 9, Pg. 125.
    - Baby Party, March 19, 1924; MS036.001.009.00001.04264; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 9)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 009, p. 6, #4251
      Students; Student activities; Baby Party; photographic print; Black students
    - Jackson College sophomore basketball team, April 14, 1924; MS036.001.009.00001.04265; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 9)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 009, p. 22, #4273
      Students; Women; Athletics; Basketball; photographic print; Black students; Jackson College
    - Jackson College sophomore basketball team, April 14, 1924; MS036.001.009.00001.04266; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 9)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 009, p. 23, #4275
    - Jackson College sophomore basketball team, April 14, 1924; MS036.001.009.00001.04267; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 9)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 009, p. 24, #4272
      Women; Students; Athletics; Basketball; photographic print; Black students; Jackson College
    - Tufts football team, October 28, 1924; MS036.001.009.00001.04268; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 9)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 009, p. 104, #4559
    - C. R. Taylor, football player, October 7, 1924; MS036.001.009.00001.04269; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 9)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 009, p. 111, #4522
      Students; Men; Athletics; Football; photographic print; Black students; Taylor, C. R.
    - E. L. Sneider, L. Sisson, P. W. Franklin, Florence L. Byrd, class of 1928, October 8, 1924; MS036.001.009.00001.04270; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 9)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 009, p. 130, #4550
      Women; Students; photographic print; Black students; Sneider, E. L.; Sisson, L.; Franklin, P. W.; Byrd, Florence L.; Jackson College
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 10, 1924-11 -- 1925-03; MS036.001.010.00001 (Volume 10)
    Alpha Omicron Pi photos of members, p74-75. Alpha Xi Delta photos of members p108-109
    - George E. Prevost, Samuel H. Levigne, Merrill J. Carter, John F. Reilly, class of 1927, November, 1924; MS036.001.010.00001.04272; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 10)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 010, p. 8, #4620
      Students; Men; photographic print; Black students; Prevost, George E.; Levigne, Samuel H.; Carter, Merrill J.; Reilly, John F.
    - George E. Prevost, Samuel H. Levigne, Merrill J. Carter, John F. Reilly, class of 1927, November, 1924; MS036.001.010.00001.04273; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 10)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 010, p. 8, #4621
    - Joseph W. Kenny, Robert B. Mills, Cuthbert C. Phillibert, Sidney P. Cohen, class of 1927,November, 1924; MS036.001.010.00001.04274; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 10)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 010, p. 10a, #4648
      Students; Men; photographic print; Black students; Kenny, Joseph W.; Mills, Robert B.; Phillibert, Cuthbert C.; Cohen, Sidney P.
    - Joseph W. Kenny, Robert B. Mills, Cuthbert C. Phillibert, Sidney P. Cohen, class of 1927, November, 1924; MS036.001.010.00001.04275; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 10)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 010, p. 10a, 4649